(this["webpackJsonphacktj-2020"]=this["webpackJsonphacktj-2020"]||[]).push([[11],{170:function(e,a,t){"use strict";t.r(a);var n=t(0),o=t.n(n),r=t(11),s=(t(83),Object(n.memo)((function(e){var a=e.question,t=e.answer,s=e.small,l=Object(n.useState)(!1),i=Object(r.a)(l,2),c=i[0],u=i[1];return o.a.createElement("li",{className:"question-group ".concat(c?"is-open":"")},o.a.createElement("h3",{className:"question ".concat(s?"small":""),onClick:function(){return u(!c)}},a,o.a.createElement("div",{className:"icon icon-plus"}),o.a.createElement("div",{className:"icon icon-close"})),o.a.createElement("div",{className:"answer",style:{maxHeight:c?"700px":0}},o.a.createElement("p",null,t)))})));t(84),a.default=function(){return o.a.createElement(o.a.Fragment,null,o.a.createElement("a",{className:"anchor",id:"faq"},"FAQ"),o.a.createElement("section",{className:"green faq"},o.a.createElement("div",{className:"container"},o.a.createElement("div",{className:"animation-container vertical left top"},o.a.createElement("div",{className:"animated white"})),o.a.createElement("div",{className:"header-row"},o.a.createElement("div",{className:"animation-container horizontal left-side"},o.a.createElement("div",{className:"animated left white"})),o.a.createElement("h1",{className:"section-title"},"FAQ"),o.a.createElement("div",{className:"animation-container horizontal right-side"},o.a.createElement("div",{className:"animated left white"}))),o.a.createElement("ul",{className:"faq-container"},o.a.createElement("div",{className:"row"},o.a.createElement(s,{question:"What is HackTJ?",answer:o.a.createElement("span",null,"HackTJ is a student-run hackathon where you will have 24 hours to learn how to code and/or work with your friends to make your idea come to life.")}),o.a.createElement(s,{question:"When is HackTJ?",answer:o.a.createElement("span",null,"HackTJ will start on Saturday, March 21 and run until Sunday, March 22. Check-in closes at 1pm on Saturday. We will not allow entry after this time.")}),o.a.createElement(s,{question:"Who can attend?",answer:o.a.createElement("span",null,"HackTJ is open to any and all current high school students. If you're not a high school student but would like to attend, consider coming as a judge, mentor, or volunteer.")})),o.a.createElement("div",{className:"row"},o.a.createElement(s,{question:"Is there any cost?",answer:o.a.createElement("span",null,"Nope! Thanks to our sponsors, HackTJ is completely free!")}),o.a.createElement(s,{question:"Is there a deadline?",answer:o.a.createElement("span",null,"Registration for participants, judges, mentors, and volunteers opens on February 10 at 8 p.m. Registration for participants closes on February 24. Judges, mentors, and volunteers will be able to register until the start of the event.")}),o.a.createElement(s,{question:"Do you have a code of conduct?",small:!0,answer:o.a.createElement("span",null,"Yes, good question! We have adopted the"," ",o.a.createElement("a",{href:"/conduct.pdf",target:"_blank",rel:"noopener noreferrer"},"MLH code of conduct"),", which all attendees will be required to adhere to.")})),o.a.createElement("div",{className:"row"},o.a.createElement(s,{question:"Isn't hacking illegal?",answer:o.a.createElement("span",null,'In the context of a hackathon, "hacking" is to build a real application over the length of the event. It\'s important to not confuse this with illegal hacking, which is gaining unauthorized access to a computer.')}),o.a.createElement(s,{question:"Do I need a team?",answer:o.a.createElement("span",null,"If you already have a team of 2-4 people you want to work with, that's awesome! If not don't worry because we'll have an opportunity for people to join a team if they need one.")}),o.a.createElement(s,{question:"What if I don't know how to code?",small:!0,answer:o.a.createElement("span",null,"Come to HackTJ! Coding is fun, creative, and an important skill, and HackTJ is the perfect way to learn. We'll have workshops and mentors to help guide you.")})),o.a.createElement("div",{className:"row"},o.a.createElement(s,{question:"What should I bring?",answer:o.a.createElement("span",null,"You'll need to bring your laptop, phone, chargers, a sleeping bag/pillow, toiletries, and extra clothing. We suggest you bring a set of nice clothes for demos; you'll want to make the best impression.")}),o.a.createElement(s,{question:"Will there be food?",answer:o.a.createElement("span",null,"Yes. Lots and lots of food.")}),o.a.createElement(s,{question:"What if I have dietary concerns?",small:!0,answer:o.a.createElement("span",null,"We'll be providing meals for most everyone at HackTJ, but if you have special concerns please"," ",o.a.createElement("a",{href:"mailto:hello@hacktj.org"},"let us know"),".")})),o.a.createElement("div",{className:"row"},o.a.createElement(s,{question:"What hardware will be available?",small:!0,answer:o.a.createElement("span",null,"All of the hardware at HackTJ is generously provided by MLH. Our list is not finalized yet, but you can browse through the usual offerings at"," ",o.a.createElement("a",{href:"https://hardware.mlh.io/",target:"_blank",rel:"noopener noreferrer"},"hardware.mlh.io"),". In previous years we\u2019ve had multiple Raspberry Pi and Arduino kits, powerful computers, Oculus headsets, Amazon Echos, Google Homes, and various sensors, motors, wires, etc.")}),o.a.createElement(s,{question:"What prizes can I win?",answer:o.a.createElement("span",null,"HackTJ hosts prizes for the best projects in the following categories: Overall Hack, Web App, Mobile App, Hardware Hack, Design, Social Impact Hack, and Beginner Hack (first-year coder teams). Major League Hacking and some of our partners also host their own Sponsored Prizes, which you can explore when the 7.0 Devpost goes live.")}),o.a.createElement(s,{question:"Can I be a mentor, judge, or volunteer?",small:!0,answer:o.a.createElement("span",null,"Mentors work interactively with students to help them develop their projects. This could mean brainstorming ideas, teaching students new skills or languages, and troubleshooting when they run into obstacles. If you have any experience with CS and are available at any time during HackTJ, you can be a mentor! Judges listen to student pitches during our Sunday-morning expo and decide which projects are winners. Experience is preferred but not necessary. Volunteers help our team with logistical tasks such as check-in, food service, and chaperoning. No experience is necessary to be a volunteer. Registration for these roles will open in March, but you can reach out to"," ",o.a.createElement("a",{href:"mailto:hello@hacktj.org",target:"_blank",rel:"noopener noreferrer"},"hello@hacktj.org")," ","in advance to be notified when the form is available!")})),o.a.createElement("div",{className:"row"},o.a.createElement(s,{question:"How do I register?",answer:o.a.createElement("span",null,'At 8 p.m. on February 10, a button will appear at the top of the site. Click this, and then you will be redirected to a page where you can click the appropriate form. If you\'re interested in participating as a hacker in HackTJ, click the first button, that says "Participants". Fill out the questions. Near the end, there will be a few questions where you can upload your forms. In order to speed up the registration process, print out these forms, fill them out, and scan them beforehand.')}),o.a.createElement(s,{question:"Wasn't HackTJ cancelled?",small:!0,answer:o.a.createElement("span",null,"Overnight events are not allowed in Fairfax County Public Schools schools. However, Cvent has graciously donated their office to us for HackTJ. HackTJ 7.0 will remain overnight!")}),o.a.createElement(s,{question:"How are tickets decisions made?",small:!0,answer:o.a.createElement("span",null,"Tickets decisisons are made based on a variety of factors, including the registration time. Sign up quickly to increase the chance that you are given a HackTJ 7.0 ticket!")}))),o.a.createElement("div",null),o.a.createElement("p",{className:"large bottom-question"},"If your question is not answered here, just ask us:"," ",o.a.createElement("a",{href:"mailto:hello@hacktj.org",target:"_blank",rel:"noopener noreferrer"},"hello@hacktj.org"),"."),o.a.createElement("div",{className:"animation-container vertical right bottom"},o.a.createElement("div",{className:"animated white"})))))}},83:function(e,a,t){},84:function(e,a,t){}}]);
//# sourceMappingURL=11.6928fa2a.chunk.js.map